

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- **JAVASCRIPT**
- **REACT JS**
- **NEXT**
- **GIT & GITHUB**

LANGUAGE

- Portuguese Native
- English Fluent

LET'S TALK



(+351) 935197007



Lisbon - Portugal



☑ tiago.justo7@gmail.com



in <u>Linkedin</u>



GitHub



Portfolio

Tiago Justo

FRONT END DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I work since I was 18 years old in a lot of areas that lead me to stagnation and no self-fulfillment. In February 2022 I started a Web and Mobile Development course that I concluded in October of the same year. Since then, I have had an internship where I learned React js and Next js. I became passionate about Web Development and I am seeking a professional challenge, in this area, with focus, determination and resilience.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer Trainee

MERKLE DACH

JULY 2022 - OCTOBER 2022

- Development of a Blog for the company Front End team in React is.
- Conversion of the React Blog to a dynamic Blog built in Next js, using mdx files, and improving the CSS with SASS.
- Git handling in console and SourceTree.

Chairman of the Board

FPESPORTS

2020 - CURRENT

- Delegate functions to the members of the project.
- Recruitment of possible sponsors and presentation of the project
- Responsible for and mentor of curricular internships for students in technological areas.
- -Functions inherent to the position.

EDUCATION

CESAE

WEB AND MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

2022 - 2022

- -Algorithm & Programming (Java).
- -Databases (SQL).
- -Web Development- Advanced (HTML, CSS, JS(jQuery), JSON, AJAX, PHP).
- -Frontend Frameworks (Angular, Typescript).
- -Backend Frameworks (PHP Laravel, Web Services).
- -Object-oriented programming.
- -Management Systems and Web Content.
- -Application Development in Java for Android (Xamarin, .Net Core, SQLite Data Base.

IEFP alverca 12th grade

LEVEL 3 LOGISTICS TECHNICIAN

Excelentíssimos senhores

your dlown

O Sr. Tiago Justo efetuou o seu estágio na minha equipa no período compreendido entre Agosto e Novembro desempenhando a função de frontend developer. Durante todo este período desempenhou todas as suas atividades de maneira eficiente e profissional.

Sempre demonstrou a sua competência profissional, bem como uma ótima adaptação aos novos desafios e facilidade na apresentação de novas ideias.

O motivo pelo qual deixou de fazer parte da nossa equipa foi devido a uma reestruturação financeira pela qual passou o nosso quadro de funcionários, que precisou ser reduzido, não podendo assim dar continuidade para um contracto permanente.

Portanto, venho por meio desta carta de recomendação reafirmar o nosso entendimento de que algumas das suas maiores qualidades são: competência, honestidade, capacidade e idoneidade, pelo que entendemos ser a nossa obrigação recomendá-lo como uma ótima contratação para a sua empresa, na qual certamente terá muito a acrescentar.

Sem mais me despeço, João Moura – Lead Frontend Solutions Portugal na Merkle DACH